UHCL Communications Office Records
University of Houston-Clear Lake Archives & Special Collections
UHCL Communications Office Records
1974-1992
1986-1988
UHCL Communications Office
#1997-0001
Three 5" document boxes (1.5 linear feet)
University of Houston-Clear Lake Archives & Special Collections
Clippings, correspondence, and other documents in files relating to university personnel, the Houston Shaw Festival, and the Bridges Preprimary Laboratory School compiled by the UHCL Communications Office of the University of Houston Clear Lake.
Administrative History
The UHCL Communications Office is the Public Relations arm of the University of Houston Clear Lake.
Scope and Contents Note
UHCL Communications Office Records consists of clippings, correspondence, and other documents in files relating to university personnel, the Houston Shaw Festival, and the Bridges Preprimary Laboratory School.
Access Restrictions
None
Index Terms
Subjects (Persons)
Avery, Hugh P.; Calvert, Linda M.; Carter, John L.; Downs, A. Christopher; Gee, Thomas C., 1940-; Johnson, L. Todd, 1942-; Kasschau, Margaret R. (Margaret Ramsey); Keller, Frank R.; Lanasa, Philip J.; Mezzino, Michael; Ptacek, Robin; Rice, William V., Jr.; Sartorius, Lester C.; Schuhmann, Robert E.; Sobrino, Josephine; Steinbrink, John E.; Turner, Max A.; Wicker, W. Walter; Williams, Henry M.; Yao, Esther L.; Hooks, Benjamin L. (Benjamin Lawson), 1925-2010)
Subjects (Organizations)
Bridges (Juanita R.) Preprimary Laboratory School; Houston Shaw Festival; University of Houston--Clear Lake
Subjects
Education
Document Types
Articles; Newspaper clippings
Acquisition Information
Acquired from UHCL Communications Office
Detailed Description of the Collection
- UHCL Communications Office Records, 1974-1992
  - Biographical File: Avery, Hugh P., 1977-1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Biographical File: Calvert, Linda M., 1977-1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Biographical File: Carter, John M., 1976-1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Subject Series: Carter, John M., 1976-1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Biographical Features: Carter, John M., 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Biographical File: Downs, A. Christopher, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Biographical File: Downs, A. Christopher, 1979-1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Biographical File: Gee, Thomas C., 1976-1991 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Biographical File: Johnson, L. Todd, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Biographical File: Kasschau, Margaret R., 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Biographical File: Kasschau, Margaret R., 1978-1986 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Biographical File: Keller, Frank R., 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Biographical File: Lanasa, Philip J., 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Biographical File: Mezzino, Michael, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Biographical File: Ptacek, Robin, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Biographical File: Rice, William V., Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Biographical File: Sartorius, Lester C., 1979-1986 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Biographical File: Schuhmann, Robert E., 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Biographical File: Sobrino, Josephine, 1974-1981 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Biographical File: Steinbrink, John E., 1980 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Biographical File: Turner, Max A., 1980 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Biographical File: Wicker, W. Walter, 1976-1985 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Biographical File: Williams, Henry M., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Biographical File: Yao, Esther L., 1986-1992 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Biographical File: Yao, Esther L., 1978-1986 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Biographical File: Hooks, Benjamin, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Subject Series: Houston Shaw Festival-Background Information, 1979-1991 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Subject Series: Houston Shaw Festival-Background Information, 1976-1982 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Subject Series: Houston Shaw Festival-1986 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Subject Series: Houston Shaw Festival-1986 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Subject Series: Houston Shaw Festival-1987, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Subject Series: Houston Shaw Festival-1988 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Subject Series: Houston Shaw Festival-1988 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Subject Series: Houston Shaw Festival-1988 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Subject Series: Houston Shaw Festival-1988 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Subject Series: Houston Shaw Festival-1989 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Subject Series: Houston Shaw Festival-1990 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Subject Series: Houston Shaw Festival-1992 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Subject Series: Bridges (Juanita R.) Preprimary Laboratory, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)